Abhishek Patel

Full Stack Developer

Contact

Address

ETOBICOKE, Ontario, M9R 1R7

E-mail

abhiptl369@gmail.com

WWW

https://bold.pro /my/abhishek-patel-369/441

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/abhishekpatel1994/

WWW

https://github.com/abhishekptl190494

Skills

CSS, HTML, JavaScript

Python

Django, React, TypeScript

Postgres SQL, My SQL

Docker, Kubernetes

DevOps: Azure

Windows, Linux, Ubuntu

Software: Matlab, Multisim, Scilab, Keil, PROTEUS-8, Arduino, Visual Studio Code, Atom Software development professional with experience in developing and designing web applications using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Django, React, Typescript. Adept at developing and deploying complex backend systems, web services and databases with basic cloud knowledge of Docker and Kubernetes.

Work History

2022-06 -Current

Full Stack Developer

aiio Gmbh, Magdeburg, Germany

- Developed full-stack web application using Django and React, Typescript
- Developed functional databases, applications and servers to support websites on back-end.
- Maintained code quality and assisted in developing and implementing systems architecture designs, patterns, and approaches.
- Reviewed code, debugged problems, and corrected issues.

2021-06 -2021-12

Internship Student

DCC Risikoanalytik GmbH, Berlin, Germany

- Performed data analysis on risk-adjusted control groups
- Established Propensity score model using Python
- Implemented appropriate NNM method in Python to assign best matching control partner based on Propensity Score Scale

2018-06 -2019-06

Intern Engineer

ONGC Petro addition Limited, Dahei, India

- Involved integration of PLC (Programmable Logic Controller) packages with DCS (Distributed Control System)
- Created regulatory control loops, Logics with SCADA (Supervisory Control And Data Acquisition) software

2015-02 -2016-01

Instrumentation Engineer

Atlas Engineering Pvt. Ltd, Bharuch, India

- Testing, assessing, calibrating and modifying instruments e.g., Temperature, Pressure and Flow instruments
- Performed on field engineering support and

Query, Numpy, Pandas, Logistic Regression (Basic)

Languages

English

German

Gujarati

Hindi

technical analysis clarification

Education

2019-10 - 2022-09	Master of Science: ITTM BBW Hochschule - Berlin
2016-08 - 2019-06	Bachelor of Engineering Technology: Instrumentation Engineering
	Sarvajanik College of Engineering And Technology Gujarat, India
2009-08 - 2014-05	Diploma: Instrumentation Engineering Nirma University - Gujarat, India

Hobbies

Training on Udemy, learning Programming languages for the development of websites and software, Volleyball, Music, Singing, Travelling.